We will create a non-measurable subset on S1
we will use the notation p in brackets
to mean the equivalence class of p
Now, we can do this for all points, so
that we have a collection of all equivalence classes.
Using the Axiom of Choice, we can pick exactly one point from
each of these equivalence classes. This will be our non-measurable set M.
Notice now that we can form the whole circle
again by looking at all rational rotations of M
By sigma additivity, we then get the following
So then, what is mu of M?
If we take mu of M is zero, then the
measure of the unit circle must also be zero.
But if we take mu of M to be nonzero,
then the measure of the unit circle must be infinite!
It should be clear that neither of these options is a good choice.