So what we can conclude from all the trees is the following.
If we multiply all elements in F2 starting with sigma
by sigma inverse on the left, we get all of
the free group, except the elements starting with sigma inverse.
This is of course equivalent to saying that F2 is the
union of sigma inverse W sigma and W sigma inverse
But the choice for sigma was arbitrary, we could have just as
well chosen to looked at the subtree of elements starting with tau.
So we also have that F2 is the union
of tau inverse W tau and W tau inverse
Let's look at the original partition of F2 that we made.
Notice that the parts in the original partition are now disjointly
used in the two new partitions that we have found.
So what we have now is called a paradoxical decomposition. We
have split the free group F2 into five parts, took four
of them and sort of shifted two of those parts to
create two copies of F2. This is called a paradoxical decomposition