One of the essential constructions in the proof of the Banach-Tarski paradox
is the use of the free group to “duplicate” the ball. We
will see that the free group generated by two elements can be
easily divided into parts, such that they can be shifted to create
two copies of itself. This is in essence what we wil eventually
be doing with the unit sphere. So what is it?
Let's look at a definition. The free group f two
generated by two elements sigma and tau is the group
consisting of all finite products of sigma, tau and their
inverses. The identity in this group is the empty product.
These are some examples of elements.
One way to look at this group is to consider it as
a directed tree. At the root of the tree, we have the
identity element e. We can then go further down the tree by
multiplying with sigma, sigma inverse, tau or tau inverse.